#### Contact

benjaminhinora@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/benjamin-hirano-a2a789240 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

HTML

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) iQuery

# Benjamin Hirano

Senior Web & Mobile Developer, Web3 Integration Timmins

## Summary

Hello,

I am a senior full stack developer with more than 8 years of strong experience in website and webapp development using modern JS frameworks and libraries including React, Redux(saga | thunk), React Hooks, Angular, Vue, and Node/Express. I am also pretty much familiar with AWS, GCP, Heroku and AWS Amplify. Recently worked on several Blockchain projects and experienced Web3 integration, RainbowKit, and Ethereum. One of my last project were NFT minting project. I also built out many mobile apps using React Native. I am a creative & detailed person who writes clean and smart code.

Here you can learn more about my experience.

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, ES6+
- Node/Express, Python/Django, Ruby on Rails
- React, Redux(saga | thunk), React Hooks, Next.js, React Native
- Material UI, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS
- Postrgres, MySQL, NoSQL, MongoDB
- Angular 14, PrimeNG, NgRx, RxJs
- Vue2/3, Vuex, Nuxt.js
- Figma, Sketch, Zeplin
- Heroku, AWS, GCP, Vercel, Netlify
- Git, Gitlab, Bitbucket
- Jira, Trello, Asana

Always open to any challenges and learning new technologies. Creative & Hard Worker

Best, Benjamin

Experience

### Roboyo

Senior Frontend Developer

June 2019 - April 2021 (1 year 11 months)

Nuremberg, Bavaria, Germany

- Developed responsive websites and web apps based on UI/UX using React.js
- React, Redux(saga | thunk), React Hooks, Material UI, TailwindCSS, Bootstrap, Node/Express
- Postgres, MySQL, MongoDB
- Setup Heroku instances and manage pipeline

Dexterity, Inc.

Frontend Developer

July 2018 - April 2019 (10 months)

Redwood City, California, United States

- Website and web app development using React.js
- Integrated Chart libraries & implemented Charts using Chart.js, AmCharts and D3.js
- File uploading to AWS S3 and Google Cloud Storage
- API integration (REST API & GraphQL)

#### **BJIT Inc**

Full Stack Engineer

July 2012 - March 2018 (5 years 9 months)

Minato, Tokyo, Japan

- Developed static web pages using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and jQuery and PHP.
- Designed UI/UX using Photoshop and 3DsMax

## Education

Tokyo Institute of Technology

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Science · (April 2008 - 2012)